It's such a great, great pleasure.
(GRANDMASTER GRUNTING)
Where are they? They're back.
- Get 'em, get 'em. Get that thing out.
- (WEAPONS FIRING)
Go, go, open the window.
Oh, jeez, they're everywhere.
Um, yeah, I see
you've been familiarizing yourself
with our obedience disks.
It's a little invention of mine,
by the way.
You know,
some people find it kind of erotic.
Walk with me.
I'm gonna tell you something.
Uh, "obedience disks,"
I've never been crazy about that name.
It was supposed to be a placeholder
until I could think of something better,
but everybody started to call 'em
"obedience disks."
What? Guys, guys, don't just poke at it.
(CREATURES SCREECHING)
There it goes. Go quickly.
Holy cats.
Here's what I wanna know. Who are you?
I am the God of Thunder!
- (ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
- Wow.
Jeez, I didn't hear anything,
but weren't those, like, sparkles
out of your fingers,
like lightning maybe?
- Works better with my hammer.
- Really?
We've located your cousin.
Uh, oh, good!
Yeah, come on.
There he is.
Hey, cuz.
We almost couldn't find you.
What, you been hiding?
Hi.
- (GROANS)
- GRANDMASTER: Hmm.
So...
Please.
(GROANS) I'm sorry.
You gotta admit what you did, Carlo.
- I was gambling.
- What?
It was just a small gamble.
He said it was only a small camel.
So, what did you do to a small camel?
I was gambling.
Scambling?
Scambling? I don't know what that means.
Scambling with the camel?
It was gambling.
Camping? He said he was camping.
That's not so bad.
Camping's bad, but what'd you really do?
I was gambling! Gambling!
Oh, gambling! That's not good.
Yeah.
Carlo...
- I pardon you.
- (SIGHS) Oh, thank you.
- There you go.
- Thank you. Oh, thank you.
- Don't do it again, though, right?
- No.
You're officially pardoned.
From life.
- (SCREAMING)
- (SIZZLING)
CARLO: (GROANS) Help me.
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(HULK SNORING)
Thor.
Thor. Thor.
Roll over. Roll over.
(HULK GRUNTING)
Stop.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Bad dream.
- Thor sad.
- Shut up.
- Sad Thor.
- Stop.
- Sad... Sad Thor.
- Don't.
- Thor sad.
- (GRUNTS)
I'm not sad, you idiot. I'm pissed off!
HULK: Oh.
I'm angry. I lost my father.
- I lost my hammer.
- (SCOFFS)
- HULK: Whining and crying...
- You're not even listening.
Don't kick my beads.
I'll kick whatever I want to kick.
I'll stomp on your stupid beads.
Baby man!
- Stupid idiot!
- You stupid white man!
- You know what we call you?
- No.
We call you the stupid Avenger.
- You know what they call you?
- What?
- The tiny Avenger.
- No, they do not say that.
No one's ever called me that.
You make me angry.
Don't you throw that.
Smash your head into crumbs like a rock.
- I'm warning you.
- (GRUNTS)
Lazy Butt!
Mope around. Don't want to play.
- What, are you crazy?
- Yes.
You know what? Earth does hate you.
(WEAPON THUDS)
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
Let's stop there.
You know what? I woke up this morning
thinking about a public execution.
I did. I really did.
(STUTTERING) But for now,
I'll settle for this sweet little
"Who's gonna get him first?"
So, uh, you're on the clock.
This means, "Go."
Did you not get that?
That's the universal sign.
Was I not clear?
Oh, for Heaven's sakes!
What did you make of that?
There's so many universal symbols.
This is one.
It's obviously not, uh, communicable.
What's this?
Dial it down.
That's "Dial it down." What's this?
Get out.
- No.
- Smaller?
Okay, here...
(MUTTERING SOFTLY)
Oh!
I'd like dessert.
Here's "I'd like dessert."
(MUTTERING)
That would be "I'd like dessert."
This would be...
- I won't do this any longer.
- Pay the bill.
Not "Pay the bill." This would be...
That would be "Pay the bill." This is
"Where's my check? Where's my check?"
Where's my check?