My name's Taika Waititi.
I am the director of Thor: Ragnarok.
Ultimately, this film is about
Thor, Ragnarok and his journey
into some outer space places.
People often ask me,
"Why did you become a filmmaker?"
Well, the main reason...
Just wanted to impress my mom and dad,
and to show them, "I'm not a loser!
I don't care what you say!
"I can achieve some dreams,
"not my own dreams,
but other people's dreams!
"I can get close to being J.J. Abrams.
"I know you wanted him as a son.
But you got me.
"I'm sorry I'm not J.J. Abrams."
They said, "All right, Taika!
Wish we called you J.J. Abrams!
"Would've been so much cooler.
You'd have done Star Wars."
"Well, I didn't.
All right, Mom and Dad? I didn't.
"You're stuck with me."
Okay. Now, down to the nifty-gritty.
Why did I make this film?
For kudos and followers on Twitter.
What I really wanted to do with Thor
was capture the essence of Peter Pan,
a little bit of Terminator 2,
a dash of Independence Day,
a smidgen of On Golden Pond
with a tone of Beaches,
mixed in with My Fair Lady.
So, I think I've achieved that.
At the end of the day,
when all's said and done,
the film's about
some monsters, some explosions,
pretty ladies, handsome men...
There's a Hulk.
Then it's the credits at the end
with all the names
of the people who made it.
That's what we tried to do,
and I think we did it.
That's what I wanted to achieve
with this film.
Full respect from Taika Waititi
from New Zealand.