MAN: A mark.
(SQUEALS)
(YELLS)
I'm putting together a team.
It's me, you, and it's you.
A wise king never seeks help.
- (BLEEP)
- (LAUGHTER)
It's one step. Every time it gets me.
- Oh.
- (BOTH LAUGH)
Oh!
CATE BLANCHETT: Did I get your testicle?
On! (LAUGHING)
- Are you okay?
- I'm good. I'm good. I'm good.
I'm fine.
- (LAUGHS) Sorry.
- (MAN LAUGHING)
I thought you were gone forever.
I'm glad to see you back.
(LAUGHTER)
You're ruining my disguise!
MAN: Play back.
(JEFF GOLDBLUM SCATTING)
Free style!
(LAUGHS)
Watch this.
Loki, take it away.
(BOTH SCATTING)
Hey.
- (MAN SNEEZES)
- (BELL RINGING)
(LAUGHTER)
Bless you.
- Sorry, guys.
- MAN: Cut.
I've been training for months,
but I don't think I can lift that.
Oh... (BLEEP)
- (LAUGHS)
- (BLEEP)
This is going really well.
(WOMAN LAUGHING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
I feel like we're gonna kiss.
I mean, it's so sweet, isn't it?
Ay-ay-ay!
- (BLOWS RASPBERRY)
- (MIMICS BLADES SWOOSHING)
I shouldn't make the noises
with my mouth, should I?
- (LAUGHTER)
- MAN: No, you can't make the noises.
(ROARS)
Forget it, just...
(BLANCHETT YELLS)
The whole thing's
- a (BLEEP) mess, Taika.
- (LAUGHTER)