(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
(CHEERING)
ODIN: Whosoever holds this hammer
shall possess the power of Thor.
Is that the best you can do?
THOR: I'm not as strong as you.
ODIN: No, you're stronger.
The first character that
Kevin wanted to bring to the screen
after Iron Man was Thor.
KEVIN FEIGE: He is such
a great counterpoint
to the other heroes,
he brings a sense of humor, and it was
very important to us like we had done
with the Winter Soldier before it,
like we had done with Ant-Man,
how do we take Thor
and bring him to another place?
How do we keep those stakes real,
but at the same time,
have a lot more fun with Thor?
CHRIS HEMSWORTH: I've been playing
the character seven years,
which, on one hand,
seems like a lifetime ago,
but also seems like yesterday
that we were shooting the first film.
Who are you?
It was all so new and we had no idea
if this was gonna work or there was
even gonna be an Avengers film,
or a sequel or so on.
I thought,
"I wanna do more with this character."
Thank you.
(GRUNTS)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
When Marvel approached me
they said, "We wanna really change up
the franchise.
"We wanna take Thor in a new direction.
"We want adventure
and to make it funny."
I will tower over the mountains
and bury my sword deep in Asgard's...
Hang on. Give it a second.
I remember the first time reading
the script and just laughing out loud.
I swear I'm not even moving.
It's just doing this on its own.
Yeah, cut it, great.
HEMSWORTH: The character felt different.
It's a long story,
but basically, I'm a bit of a hero.
How much longer do you think
we'll be here?
We've always, sort of, aimed for
an English dialect and tone.
But it was much more
a nod at the Shakespearean period.
I will tell Father
what you did here today.
I didn't do it for him.
HEMSWORTH: This time around,
you know, I just said to Andrew,
"Look, he's not straight off
"the ship from Asgard anymore.
"He's lived on Earth for a while.
"And so, he's got to
have a contemporary feel to him."
So, we loosened his accent.
- He's weighted down...
- When he's coming out of there.
His world is different.
It's Earth-influenced now, so he's
having to communicate with people
on this completely different level.
You don't have a phone.
No, I don't have a phone,
but you could have sent an electronic
letter. It's called an email.
- Yeah, do you have a computer?
- No. What for?
He's now grown as a hero,
where he can poke fun at himself,
where he can become much more
self-aware about his surroundings.
MAN: Action!
WINDERBAUM: We see a Thor who's been
steeped in the world of Tony Stark,
picked up sarcastic rhythms,
he's got a sense of humor.
- Banner is powerful and useful, too.
- Is he though?
WINDERBAUM: And he brings that attitude
into the stars with him.
And it's that version of Thor
that we're elaborating on in our film.
To show Chris as
the comedic force that he really is.
Oh, yes.
(CLANGING AND CRASHING)
Sorry.
MAN: Go!
ERIC PEARSON: The first shot
that we ever got in this movie,
there was Chris hanging
upside down in front of Surtur.
Immediately I could tell
he's uncomfortable.
But he's playing the scene funny.
He's actually letting the discomfort
fuel his performance.
Can we do another one, quickly?
He's got a lot of courage, that guy.
Because it takes a lot of hard work
to build up like that to play Thor.
MAN: Action.
What's good about him is
he hasn't been affected by
his great stardom and fame.
MAN: Awesome.
I get pretty bored doing the same thing
and once it feels too familiar or safe,
I think it becomes less interesting.
High-five.
(CREW LAUGHING)
(MAN SPEAKING)
He's getting to do things in this movie
that he's never been able to do.
He's recreating the character.
Everything is different,
and new, and fresh,
and what drew my interest
was knowing that
Chris was going to be
in the film, obviously.
Not just 'cause he's attractive.
Cute. He's cute.
He's cute as Christmas.
He's fun to be around.
He's a funny guy.
That was amazing.
CATE BLANCHETT: I've never met
a more generous performer than Chris.
He's incredible to work with.
He holds this whole behemoth together.
Like, a lot of us are riding on his
shoulders and what shoulders they are.
He destroys the idea of what audiences
expect from him as an actor.
- Hey, let's do "Get Help."
- No.
- Come on, you love it.
- I hate it.
- It's great. It works every time.
- It's humiliating.
- Do you have a better plan?
- No.
- We're doing it.
- We are not doing "Get Help."
Chris and I have been on this journey
together for seven years and it's
very different to any relationship
I've ever had with any other actor.
God of Thunder.
Hey.
We know each other so well
and I think, in a way,
that enhances everything about
that relationship.
We have a shorthand
and he makes me laugh.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, get out of my shot.
I'm acting here.
I pinch myself all the time
and just think,
"Man, how did I stumble upon this?"
- You guys want us to do that, right?
- No. Is that right?
- Just Mark?
- He's a God. Look at that.
What did I do right
exactly to deserve any of this?
I love it. I really do.
(ALL CHEERING)
I'd do many more of them
if people wanted to see them.
I choose to run toward my problems
and not away from them.
Because that's what...
Because that's what heroes do.