This Marvel Universe
is something fairly unique.
(GRUNTS)
It's never really been done before,
this many films interconnected.
The events of Thor: Ragnarok take place
around the same time as Civil War.
Be great if we had Hulk right about now.
So, while everything's
going to hell on Earth,
everything's literally
going to hell in space.
Hulk! Just for once in your life,
don't smash.
Big monster!
It was very important to us to
tap into the history of Marvel Comics.
I was a mad comic collector
when I was young.
And this film is
heavily influenced by that style.
WINDERBAUM:
Two comic book runs that we looked at
were the early Jack and Stan stuff,
Journey into Mystery stuff,
as well as the Walt Simonson run,
where he told
the definitive Ragnarok story.
My idea of a storyline was a mixture
of Norse mythology and Marvel mythology.
The story of Surtur and Ragnarok,
the death of the gods.
It's not exactly
the same story in our film,
but there are iconic aspects
that we're embracing.
Surtur being key to
the ultimate destruction of Asgard.
The brothers, Thor and Loki, having to
work together in order to save the day,
despite their differences.
It's the only way.
These are all things that are
really important to the Ragnarok story.
I am Asgard's doom!
You get so much information,
so many storylines from the comics.
It's really fun for me to
figure out which cool things to take.
Jack Kirby is arguably
the most important comic book artist.
We are directly referencing
a lot of his art which is very iconic.
Get him. Open a window.
FEIGE: All of the Thor films
have always been inspired by his work,
but in this particular movie,
Taika had an idea to just
really make it a tribute to Jack Kirby.
Listen, we're gonna go to Asgard...
and you're not gonna have to think about
the Hulk ever again. All right?
All right.
(CROWD CHEERING)
Hulk! Hulk!
This film, to me, seems like the perfect
environment in which to show his style.
His line, his color, everything.
It's almost as if we have finally
stepped into a Jack Kirby drawing.
WAITITI: He's created so many incredible
characters, and ships and costumes.
He really blazed the trail.
And it's about time that someone
paid tribute to him in this way.
I mean, he really was the king.
Get up. You're in my seat.
It's incredible what the character of
Hela means to the fans
and what her history
with the comics has been.
I'm Hela.
I'm just a janitor.
You look like a smart boy.
There's an incredible, fantastic element
to her power.
She was born with a rare gift
to create any number
of deadly weapons at her whim.
ERIC PEARSON: There's a run of Thor
called "God of Thunder,"
where there was a character named Gorr
going around killing gods.
And it's a really fun comic to read.
And we used a lot of the visual aspect
of Gorr's powers to infuse with Hela.
Want to see what true power
really looks like?
(GROWLS)
We were able to tap into something
from the comics which is very exciting,
which our storylines have taken Hulk
to other sides of the universe.
MARK RUFFALO:
Everybody wants Planet Hulk.
Planet Hulk is a legendary Marvel comic.
It's beloved by fans.
PEARSON: This was not going to
be the Planet Hulk movie,
but we were using elements of it
where Hulk ends up on
a very different-looking Sakaar
and is forced to be a gladiator.
We spun it and we've given
a lot of that story to Thor
while also introducing Hulk
in the same context.
(ROARS)
I really wanted to
have Hulk with battle armor,
with the shoulder pads, and the spikes,
and everything.
WINDERBAUM:
Marvel's Contest of Champions
is something we're excited to
bring to the screen for Marvel fans.
And one of the allies that Thor makes
is this Kronan named Korg.
I really wish I had my hammer.
Sounds like you had a pretty special and
intimate relationship with this hammer
and that losing it was almost comparable
to losing a loved one.
WINDERBAUM: He was a character
from the Planet Hulk storyline
and also poetically is
of the first breed of aliens
that Thor had to fight in his first
issue of Journey Into Mystery.
(ALL EXCLAIM)
Anyone else?
We kind of make this a fairly unique
film of its own and story.
But Ragnarok has already begun.
As long as you stay true
to the core of the characters,
then it's just a big playground.
For Asgard.
WAITITI: Just a chance to play around
and be a bit mad
and make it feel
a little bit more like a comic.
You can't defeat me.
But he can.
The fans are always
front-of-mind for us.
Not just the fans of today,
but also the fans from years ago.
These are characters
that have been around for decades.
So, the excitement that someone had
reading a new story for the first time
is the same excitement we hope they feel
when they go to the movies
and see the latest interpretation
of the character onscreen.