(METAL CLANGING)
The entire Marvel Cinematic Universe
started in May of 2008
with the release of Iron Man 1.
And it really is
an unprecedented journey.
LOUIS D'ESPOSITO:
It's been interesting watching
Tony Stark evolve,
there's an emotional resonance.
His relationship with
the other Avengers,
his relationship with Pepper Potts,
his relationship,
most importantly, with himself,
and how that's developed from film
to film has been quite extraordinary.
To see Tony get to a point
where he is introspective,
where he is thinking about the things
that they have saved over the years
has been amazing.
He is the heart of the Universe.
ROBERT DOWNEY JR.:
It's just been this
magical thing that occurred,
this kind of really risky idea of
bringing this whole world to life.
And I think with Thor,
you had Hemsworth in front
and there was this very sci-fi version
of a Marvel picture.
In each film, he has grown a greater
affection for Earth and humans
than the first time we saw him,
when he was arrogant.
There can be this great kind of
strength and knowledge
and power with him,
but there's also a naive kid there
at the center of it.
It's nice to have
that contrast and that mix.
His biggest concern is
the well-being of this world.
And he very much is sort of looking out
further into the universe,
to make sure that threat
doesn't consume this world as well.
I think the most challenging one
of all of them was Cap.
This kind of guy-out-of-time,
and "Is it too retro?
Are people gonna get it?"
With Evans and Johnston
the first time around,
it was like, "Yes, we get it,
and you get it and you like it."
Initially I'm just trying to build
a foundation of who this guy is.
But you feel like
you know the character now.
FEIGE: The first Captain America film
is subtitled, "The First Avenger,"
because that's really what Cap is.
Born out of the technology
of the 1940s,
frozen in ice, coming back
into the present day.
He then goes into the Avengers
and you realize, in a lot of ways, he's
the moral backbone of the Avengers.
- How do we do this?
- As a team.
(ROARS)
D'ESPOSITO: We have Thor,
Cap, the Hulk, Iron Man
finally come together in Avengers.
That was something new
that people had never seen before.
NICK FURY: There was an idea to bring together
a group of remarkable people.
See if they could work together
when we needed them to.
To fight the battles
that we never could.
For us, that's what
an Avengers movie is all about.
How are they gonna react?
Do they like each other?
Do they hate each other?
Do they get along?
Do they become instant best friends?
That is the heart and soul
of an Avengers film.
As the Universe grows,
it's really nice to grow
with the character as I have.
She has a greater calling.
MARK RUFFALO:
Each movie, I am excited
by the idea of reinventing Hulk.
Struggle and challenge
just brings out the best of us.
The first Avengers was about them
meeting each other for the first time.
In Age of Ultron, they're getting to
know each other for the first time.
There is a real sense of unity
between the Avengers at this point,
so there's something to attack.
My favorite part about
Avengers: Age of Ultron is
a feeling of ending of an era
and the beginning of another,
leading to Captain America: Civil War.
Civil War was primarily a conflict
between Steve Rogers and Tony Stark.
Cap went from being this guy
who was built by the government
and his allegiance
was to the government,
and it was a blind allegiance.
And Tony was kinda always
flipping the bird to the government,
doing what he wanted to do.
And was kind of
this rogue entrepreneur,
and over the course
of these movies now,
it's just kind of evolved,
and the tables have turned a bit.
JOE RUSSO: Civil War was
an incredibly impactful event
that had major ramifications in the
Avengers and in the Marvel Universe.
It's fun to take the characters
that exist to new places.
And then it's equally exciting
to bring in the new players.
And that's why things like
Doctor Strange,
things like Guardians of the Galaxy,
allows you to keep expanding
the tone as you go.
I think all of that just builds
the sort of mystique and mystery
that is part of every movie
that they do.
There is just quite
a great emotional journey
within the films.
What we've seen happen within the
Marvel Universe is this ever-expanding
coterie of superheroes.
And I think now we're at the stage
where this universe, even with
our world, has got quite crowded,
and it's just about to explode
into other dimensions.
TONY: I was shown my legacy.
The end of the path I started us on.
Everyone has their
favorite Marvel movie,
and everyone has their
favorite Marvel world,
and just to see
all of them coming together,
it's a daring act.
Who the hell are you guys?
Every story that Marvel has told
since Iron Man 1
finds a narrative thread
in these next two Avengers movies.
It is a culmination of
all of that storytelling.
With Infinity War, we're paying off
every little thread
and every little tease that we've had
in what will be 18 films
prior to Infinity War.
There's never been anything like this,
being able to, film after film,
tease at a larger story,
really building these stories
up into a giant conclusion.
While at the same time,
introducing an entirely
new direction for the future.