Sakaar is this crazy alien world.
It's wacky and feels like this sci-fi,
high-tech insanity.
It's a physics phenomenon.
And we're stranded on a planet
that is designed to stress me out.
It's lawless and chaotic,
but in a completely hilarious way,
where nothing makes any sense.
WOMAN: Sakaar lives on the edge
of the known and unknown.
It's something you've never
seen on film before.
What the hell?
Three, two, one...
- Boom!
- (GUNFIRE)
WAITITI:
When Marvel approached me, they said,
"We wanna take Thor in a new direction."
(GRUNTS)
(LAUGHING)
We wanted to have more fun with Thor.
Take him out of Asgard and take him
to another side of the universe.
Sakaar couldn't be more different
than Asgard in every respect.
It's a hyper-color
science-fiction circus of a planet
that is the toilet of the universe.
WOMAN: Surrounded by cosmic gateways,
it is the collection point
for all lost and unloved things.
Those wormholes are
dropping space debris
onto the surface of the planet.
And the population,
over thousands of years,
have repurposed and made the city.
This might be the most audacious set
we've ever built,
for the most audacious planet
that we've ever featured
in one of our films.
When you look at the design
of this whole place, from these walls,
to the costumes, to the little props,
it is entirely a tribute to
the artistry of Jack Kirby.
CROWD: (CHANTING)
Hulk! Hulk! Hulk!
Take to the streets.
Celebrate my champion.
Who's that?
He kind of runs the place.
Sakaar is ruled by the Grandmaster,
played by Jeff Goldblum.
And he's insane,
and colorful, and hilarious.
I pardon you. From life.
(SCREAMING)
HIDDLESTON: The Grandmaster is
the photo negative of Odin.
He's a very high-status figure.
He does things with disco.
Grandmaster improvises.
One, two, three, four...
I'm practicing now, this little section
which includes me as Grandmaster
playing with a band.
WINDERBAUM: We wanted that character
to be really memorable,
and Goldblum's just perfect.
I'm going back to Asgard.
Ass-gard?
I can't say that I'm all that familiar.
He turned up, clay one,
and blew us all away.
- Ass-place, Assberg...
- Asgard.
GOLDBLUM:
I'll tell you this, and this is honest,
it was as good a time as I've ever had.
Champion, champion, champion...
GOLDBLUM: It was really fun, exciting,
and I liked what we were doing.
And cut.
(LAUGHING)
Look at all of you. Who's having fun?
We were able to tap into something from
the comics which is very exciting.
Hulk!
Marvel's Contest of Champions
is a favorite book.
You got to see your heroes
face off against each other.
It was the inspiration for one of the
best action scenes we've ever produced.
Yeah, they go at it for a bit.
(GROWLING)
Go!
(GRUNTS)
(ROARS)
With Hulk's history in the comics
of these cosmic adventures,
we felt like, the perfect choice
to bring him into that Thor world.
The idea of those two heroes together
is probably the one thing that got me
the most excited about the project.
You're Banner's friend.
I'm not Banner's friend. I prefer you.
Thor, Banner's friend.
Hulk's no longer depending
on Banner's anger.
Hulk trains.
That's great. Have fun.
Hey, big guy-
On Sakaar, he's a huge star.
He's a prizefighter.
And he gets the penthouse suite
and anything he wants, basically.
This is Hulk's suite.
Hulk's bed is basically
an old dragon's skull.
Something that he's put together,
a bit of a prize.
He loves sleeping there.
He's the guy who can afford
whatever he wants
and space is of a premium in Sakaar.
Stupid place. It's hideous, by the way.
The red, the white. Just pick a color.
Ridiculous.
Smash you.
Hulk's a lot more articulate in this
movie than we've ever seen him before.
I'm sorry.
I just get so angry all the time.
Hulk always angry.
Hulk is a CG character, but because
we capture Mark's performance,
he has a nuanced way of being
that you don't expect
from a big, green monster.
(ROARING)
- Cut. Great.
- Cut!
Mark Ruffalo brings the gravity
to Bruce Banner.
Mark Ruffalo reinvented Banner,
reinvented the Hulk.
His playfulness, I think, is what
people will really get a kick out of.
Last time I saw you,
you were trying to kill everybody.
Where are you at these days?
It varies from moment to moment.
It was very fun to see, for
the first time, Loki and Hulk reunited
under very different circumstances than
the last time we saw them.
I am a god, you dull creature.
One of my favorite things in this film
is Loki's response to Hulk smashing Thor
in exactly the same way
that Loki got smashed.
Yes! Come on!
That's how it feels! Whoo!
You feel that?
Come on, this place is perfect for you.
It's savage, it's chaotic, it's lawless.
Do you truly think so little of me?
(LAUGHING)
WINDERBAUM:
Pan' of the fun of Loki is that
he rides that line between
protagonist and antagonist.
One second, he's on your side,
and the other second he's doing
something that serves only himself.
There's a bit of a running gag in
the comic books and the previous films
about Thor's trusting him again
and he's betraying him again.
(LAUGHING)
(GRUNTS)
You still don't trust me, bother.
- Would you?
- No, I wouldn't.
Classic Loki.
THOR: There was one time
when we were children...
he transformed himself into a snake,
and he knows I love snakes.
So, I went to pick up the snake
to admire it...
and he transformed back into himself
and he was like, "Yeah, it's me!"
And he stabbed me.
In Ragnarok, actually, Thor has sort of
cottoned on to the cycle.
And Loki has to adapt
for perhaps the first time.
You'll always be the God of Mischief...
but you could be more.
I think, inherently,
there is good in Loki.
But he just has a warped view
and entitlement.
We're about to jump on that
ginormous spaceship. You wanna come?
Well, you do seem like you're
in desperate need of leadership.
HIDDLESTON:
Every time I play Loki,
and this is a source of constant
surprise and delight to me, is that,
people love him so much.
(CHEERING)
(MOUTHS INAUDIBLY)
And I think it's because people
can relate to him in some way.
He's an outsider. He's a misfit.
- Yes!
- MAN: Cut!
Did you see that? Did you see that?
- Come on.
- HEMSWORTH: Nice catch.
Well, what's always fun is
the comics were so amazing
having a shared universe.
Where anybody could show up
in anybody else's book.
Yes!
Kevin Feige and all the guys at Marvel
always love going somewhere different.
Just had to see where we can take it.
(SCREAMING)
In these films,
they are able to find new ways
of those characters interacting
and fighting
and teaming up and having a laugh
in all kinds of new places.
Get help!
Classic.
- It's humiliating.
- Not for me, it's not.
HEMSWORTH: And Sakaar is
the perfect coming together
of these characters
in the Marvel Universe.
It's my birthday
This wasteland world of Sakaar is
the wild, epic space-adventure aspect
of Thor that we haven't seen
onscreen before.
Guys, we're coming up
on the Devil's Anus!