Oh, I've missed this.
Here we go.
This is not the film you're expecting.
This is not the Thor
that you are used to.
Kneel.
In this film,
we have strong female characters.
Don't get familiar.
That makes for a far more interesting
journey to watch.
(GRUNTS)
It's not possible.
You have no idea what's possible.
- What have you done?
- I don't answer to you, lackey.
It's Loki.
And you will answer to the Grandmaster.
- (GROANS)
- Hmm.
WAITITI: Nowadays, we just need
more female actors in films.
Not just characters who look good
in armor and look good
holding a sword, but actually
hold their own against the other guys.
MARK RUFFALO: We have Cate Blanchett
and we have Tessa Thompson,
these two amazing, powerful,
strong, beautiful, intelligent women,
playing these two important,
integral characters.
Want to see what true power
really looks like?
We are introducing what we think is
one of the most iconic villains
in the history of Marvel Comics, Hela.
Who is the first female villain
that we've had in a Marvel film.
BRAD WINDERBAUM: Hela is a badass.
Just a character you want to see
more of onscreen that's so charismatic.
But at the same time,
you're afraid
of what she's gonna do next.
She is as scary, and deadly,
and charming as any
villain we've ever had.
I am Hela, Odin's firstborn...
the commander
of the Legions of Asgard...
the rightful heir to the throne,
and the Goddess of Death.
WINDERBAUM: When you're bringing
a character as iconic as Hela
from the Marvel comics to the screen,
you need an actor who
could be the best villain
we've ever had.
So, Cate Blanchett
was obviously the first choice.
It seems our father's solution
to every problem was to cover it up.
Or to cast it out.
HEMSWORTH: Cate Blanchett is
one of, if not the, greatest actors.
And I was so excited to see
what she was gonna do.
To have this villainess
be introduced in such a strong way
is really exciting.
CATE BLANCHETT: I've had incredible fun
playing with her.
Because I think
her capabilities are so surprising
and so unusual,
she's not simply sinister.
MAN: Action!
(GRUNTS)
As somebody who's played the villain
in these films,
I understand the responsibilities,
and she has a huge presence,
which she can express
physically or verbally.
I'm throwing you. Isn't... Is the...
She just has this
off-kilter movement to her character
I was completely blindsided by it.
Some of the happiest times
have been beating people up.
(GRUNTING)
So it's been good.
I think it's great that there is
an elite force of women warriors.
It's about time.
WINDERBAUM: Valkyrie is a big deal for us.
Bringing her to the big screen,
and having her be a new force
in the Marvel Universe,
a new, great female heroine
who can lead the charge
for the next generation of the MCU.
The Valkyrie were Amazonian.
They were invincible.
They were truly extraordinary beings.
You're a Valkyrie.
(GRUNTS)
I thought the Valkyrie had all died
gruesome deaths.
Choose your next words wisely.
THOMPSON: What Taika and what Marvel
has been willing to do
is also stretch the parameters
and find a Valkyrie that's new
- and fresh.
- And... Okay.
I smiled 'cause it felt like
I was on a runway.
(LAUGHING)
Today, we're working on kicks
and technique,
and these things, sort of tricks
and spins and stuff.
Every day, there's something that's
easier and something that's harder.
I just tell myself a little affirmation,
"You can do this.
It's just a little wind."
THOMPSON: We wanted to find a style
that feels different
than the way that you see
most women fighting in film in general.
(GRUNTING)
I would say that she fights like a boy
except that diminishes the fact
that she just fights like
a really, really strong woman.
Tessa has thrown herself at this
in the most extraordinary way.
Just incredible commitment
to the physicality of the part.
The minute she opened the door,
I went, "Wow, this one's got a history."
Tessa was so compelling
and powerful, and mysterious.
Cut.
We talk so much in Hollywood
about representation of women
and we need really strong,
stand-out parts for women.
But we also need women that are
in conflict and are not so great.
MAN: Go!
(GRUNTS)
We need representation
all across the board.
You're in my seat.
Women are as capable
and as strong as we are anyway.
And so, they gave in the film,
a different energy.
In this film and in more Marvel films,
we're starting to see women
in these big, heroic parts.
It is inspiring for everybody.
Especially the kids.
To be honest, I expected more.
(GRUNTING)
(ELECTRICITY SIZZLING)